It's really sharp.
It's totally different from what I usually do.
It's camellia.
Camellia?
It's so cute!
It's too cute!
Hello, I'm Ayaka Takamoto.
Where do you think I am today?
I'm at Jean!
I'm at Kappa Marsh. Look at this!
This is the cook.
The reason why I'm here is because
I have a dream that I want to fish by myself.
I've been thinking about getting a kitchen knife.
I thought I might be able to find a knife that suits me
here I am!
Yay!
I'm going on a journey to find a kitchen knife!
I'm off!
Kappabashi Tool Street
Kappa-bashi tool-gai street.
Oh, oh, that Kappa is here.
Kappa.
Oh, Kappa!
Kappa!
Wow, there's so many kappas!
So cute!
Oh, so many amazing plates! I don't have that many plates.
I always use the same plates. Oh, Kappa!
There's a kappa here. Nakagawa kappa.
Kappa Nakagawa!
I'd love to introduce you to Bread Tool Store Meepan
Bread... Mee-pan... Mee-pan... here's some bread-making tools.
MeePan and I have always wanted to catch tuna.
I hope to handle tuna someday. I caught it myself.
Wow, this is a really stylish building.
We've arrived at Kamaasa Shoten.
I'd like to see the knives. Excuse me.
Excuse me. It's cool.
It's so stylish... but there are so many knives.
There are so many knives
Wow... ah...
A thermoslicer.
Is this the one that slices fish?
Fish? I don't know.
Knife at the ready.
Peppy.
Knives for the first time
Santoku, Gyuto, Peppy
I have this one, but I use a 100 yen one, this tiny one.
I have about two of these santoku knives, which are a common shape.
Western knives are good for cutting quickly and evenly.
Japanese knives are single-edged and do not damage the fibers.
The Japanese knife is single-edged and beautifully finishes the cross section without damaging the fibers.
There are many other types of knives for different purposes.
Bread knife, salmon knife
Large fish
If you want to cut fish, you should use a de-eba knife.
I want to cut fish.
Okay, I'll wait for you.
You can cut fish at home, right?
Most people use a de-aberu knife with a blade length of about 15 cm, called a 5-sun knife.
A 6"5 kitchen knife.
The weight is quite different.
From big to small, I think this 5 inch knife is the easiest to use.
This is about right for you.
I think you can use it for a long time if you choose a knife with the right weight and balance for your hand.
I see.
The back is steel, isn't it?
Steel.
There are two kinds, steel and stainless steel.
Steel is good for sashimi, but the blade tends to come out easily.
You need to take care of it after use.
I see.
When the blade is cut and not used for a long time, it is time to stick oil firmly on the blade
You will know how to cut well
It's a lot of work!
A store that requires a lot of time and effort is a stainless steel shop.
A stainless steel store is a stainless steel store
Wow, do all kitchen knives cost this much?
The price depends on the size and the material of the blade.
I see.
I'm surprised.
I've never had such an expensive knife before, so I'm surprised.
I'm curious about it because I don't have a steel one, but it seems like it would be hard to take care of.
It's cool, really.
I'm going to get all of them out of the box. If I buy such a nice one, I'll be
Awesome.
Thank you for watching.
Can you cut sashimi with this?
Yes, it can.
This is three swords.
Five rows of knives, four knives in all.
With these small knives and so on.
Yes, that kind of thing.
Yes, sir.
It's very easy to cut, isn't it?
Yes.
When I cut fences or sashimi at home, I use a knife to cut the fish.When I cut fences or sashimi at home, I use a normal knife.
I use an ordinary knife.
When I use a knife to make sashimi
When I make sashimi
I use a normal knife.
I can't get a good cut at the end.
If you have a Yanagiba knife
I think the quality of the sashimi would be improved
If you have it...
Hmmm...
Seeing this...
I feel like cutting something.
Um, can you cut something?
I don't usually do that.
If you don't mind.
Thank you very much.
I can cut something for you.
Yay!
IANAGIwa knife hassun
crate 生煎 н刀奏
Yes, ma'am.
Slicing Kamatos
HASSUN Jook's IANAGIwa knife
Let me try to slice it ah, thank you
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow.
It doesn't usually cut like this.
I'd like to do a little more
Wow, it feels so good!
That's amazing.
Tomatoes are so hard to cut.
It's hard to get a good cross-section of the tomato outside of the skin.
But even if you cut a tomato from this area...
It's so beautiful!
How is this possible?
Wow!
You can slice tomatoes so thin, it's like sashimi.
Wow, it's so much fun! It's so sharp!
It's totally different from what I usually do. I was surprised to find such a sharp knife.
I'm going to cut carrots with a deba knife.
Wow!
Carrots are like this!
You can cut like this.
It's not an ingredient.
Wow!
Amazing!
That's great!
It takes a lot of strength.
It doesn't take much.
It's so easy to use.
I wish I had one like this.
I want it so much!
I'm really impressed.
It was an amazing encounter.
The sharpness...
I mean, it's great, but...
It's going to be a very expensive purchase.
I'll have to think seriously about it one more time
I think I'll make a decision.
Thank you very much for letting me cut it.
It was a wonderful encounter.
Thank you very much.
That was really cool.
It's really cool.
It's so easy to cut.
I'm really, really wanting to get one.
I've heard that I can visit one more store.
I heard they have colorful knives next.
I'll have a look at that too.
I'd like to see them and make a decision.
Here we are!
Wow, something smells good.
Excuse me. Pleased to meet you.
Hello.
It's really colorful. Wow, the store is dark and stylish.
Wow, there are so many kitchen knives,
There are some sun-colored knives over there.
Wow.
They look great, but they cut right off.
I see.
Well then.
Ninety-four thousand yen. Amazing.
Forty-four thousand yen.
When you hold it in your hand, you can feel its weight,
Japanese kitchen knives are usually light,
But Japanese kitchen knives are usually light, so they have a little weight and grip.
That's right.
When you compare them, they are all heavy.
Wow, this is amazing. This is so beautiful.
Wow. Is that a flower pattern? That one.
It's a camellia.
Camellia?
Wow. Camellia is so cute.
It's painted with screws, and it's all rimmed.
Wow, it's so cute.
Too cute now.
It's getting erotic.
I want to handle the fish,I want to process fish,
Is it possible to cut it here?
Is it possible to cut fish around here?
It's not hard to cut,
What size of fish do you want to process?
Like a sea bream.
If it's a sea bream or something like that, I might be more careful with the liver.
I see.
Liver requires a lot of force,
I think the part you grip may be more important.
Yes, that's right.
So, it should not be too big.
I see.
It's not really a fateful encounter,
But we will be together for a long time,
That's right.
The best way is to bring home a girl you like.
I understand. Difficult.
Thank you very much.
Wow, that was amazing.
I really wanted to buy all kinds of knives,
I'm in a state of wanting so many different knives that I'm looking at them so much that I don't know what to do with them.
I am going to buy one with my own money,
I was seriously worried about it,
I really thought about knives when I came here today,
I was surprised at how expensive they are. I was surprised at how expensive they are.
I was really surprised at how expensive they were. I was surprised.
Hmmm.
What should I do - I'm troubled.
I'm troubled - I'm troubled. What shall I do?
It's disgusting.
Nervous.
It's so painful!
I wonder if they'll think I'm back. I'm back.
Excuse me. I was thinking of buying that Deva knife.
May I take another look at it? Yes, please.
Peralest from here.
Can you handle sea bream with this?
If the bones are hard, it may chip a little depending on how you use it.
Oh, is that so? Is it still okay this way?
It's still thicker.
I see.
I'll go with this one.
This way.
Thank you.
This knife is priced at
2,396 yen.
A little cash. I didn't have any cash on hand. Please use your card.
That was expensive!
That's great!
I'll take it.
Wow! Cool!
Look at all of you!
Ayaka! My knife is done! Yay!
Yay! I'm so happy!
It cost 20,000 yen!
I bought it myself!
It's 20,000 yen for me and everyone who will be doing YouTube from here on out.
I'm going to continue to send out messages with the weight of my commitment.
I would like to continue to send out messages with a heavy heart!
I'm getting really excited about cooking.
I think I'm going to like cooking even more!
The next step is to process the fish.
The only way is to process the fish, so I definitely want to do it!
Please subscribe to my channel and give me high ratings!
Bye bye bye!
Next time I'm going to fish!